tfltruck.com 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy - Truck News, Views and Real World Reviews

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or participate in contest.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

– To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

– To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

– To send periodic emails

When subscribing to a newsletter, the email address you provide may be used to send you periodic updates on new content on our site.

**Do we use cookies?**

We do not use cookies.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [http://www.tfltruck.com](http://www.tfltruck.com/)

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [web site privacy policy](http://www.tfltruck.com/privacy-policy).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on dec-08-2013

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

http://www.tfltruck.com  
info@tflcar.com
